<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Jonas Eduardsen</title>
    <link>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 15:09:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>AIB 2022</title>
      <link>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/aib-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 15:09:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/aib-2022/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Next week I will be participating in the annual Academy of International Business Conference in Miami, which is hosted by Florida International University. The theme this year is &amp;lsquo;Beyond Diversity and Inclusion: Equity and Fairness in International Business&amp;rsquo;. Thus, there will be ample opportunity to discuss how IB scholars can increasingly integrate Equity and Fairness into IB research and the post-pandemic globalization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the conference, I will be presenting some preliminary findings from my research on cross-border e-commerce in European firms, where I explore heterogeneity in managerial perceptions of barriers to cross-border e-commerce across firms, industries, and countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will be the first time since 2019 in Copenhagen where the conference will take place physically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to read more about the conference you can do so &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aib.world/events/2022/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New research article</title>
      <link>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jonaseduardsen.github.io/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m happy to share a recent publication that I have written together with my colleagues Svetla Marinova, Bozidar Vlacic and Miguel Gonzalez Loureiro which have been accepted for publication in International Business Review and is now available online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study is one of few studies that examine the role of business group affiliation on SMEs international sales intensity and diversification in developed economies. The study uses a multi-country sample of over 13,000 European SMEs from 34 different countries to examine under what conditions business group affiliation is beneficial to the international sales of SMEs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The publication can be downloaded free of charge using the link below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lnkd.in/g3b2YSq8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://lnkd.in/g3b2YSq8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
